Zzzz｡.(⁎ꈍ﹃ꈍ⁎)･*
Oooo｡.(⁎ ´0｀⁎)･*
No uniform today, that's okay, right?
Spreading margarine is okay, right?
Forget the routine, just stick out your tongue!
Despite how I look, I might be a bad girl, you know?
Sleeping twice, three times, as many times as you want — that's okay
Even showing up in pajamas is okay
Puffing up my chest, feeling like I've won
This isn't like me at all
Ready, go!
Pi pi pi, sparkling, sparkling (sparkling)
Ka ka ka, busy busy (busy busy)
Ta ta ta ta, fluttering about
Hey, are you looking the other way?
Hey, good work today!
Don't push yourself too hard
Samba with a tambourine
( 'ω' و( و"♪
A cute girl just like this
On a silly vacation, fast asleep
Don't push yourself too hard
Don't push yourself today
Carnival every day
With a shy smile
Let's take it easy
※Sorry, it's vacation time...₊˚ˑ༄
.　〃∩ ∧＿∧
⊂⌒(　=•ω•)
＼_ っ📖c
⋆˚☆˖°⋆⭒˚｡
‧₊˚ ⭒ ˚˖°⋆
Ooh, Yeah!
Pi pi pi, sparkling, sparkling (sparkling)
Ka ka ka, busy busy (busy busy)
Ta ta ta ta, fluttering about (fluttering)
That's so silly
I'm so fed up
Heart pounding (heart pounding)
Actually, sometimes (heart pounding)
My heart is pounding
Well then, doesn't that mean that kind of thing?
Don't push yourself too hard
Samba with a tambourine
( 'ω' و( و"♪
A cute girl just like this
Broadcasting on all channels
Don't push yourself too hard
Don't push yourself today
Everything and anything
Dragging on and on
Anxious and unstable
I'm so fed up!
Don't push yourself too hard (too hard)
Samba with a tambourine
Sorry about being like this
On a silly vacation, fast asleep
Don't push yourself too hard (too hard)
Look, let's all do it together
Start a happy day
I am the teacher
Let's take it easy
Carnival every day
With a shy smile
Let's take it easy!
Thank you for listening:))